Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Chronological press releases, 1954-1959; 1973-2022; Series I.; 4.06 Linear Feet (8 boxes); 0.99 GB (2,249 files)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust:
    - 2001:
      - September-December (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 49)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Winter (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 50)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Spring (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 51)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Summer (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 52)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Fall (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 53)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Winter 2001-2002 (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 54)
    - 2002:
      - Schedule and distribution (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 55)
      - January-February (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 56)
      - March-May (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 57)
      - June-September (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 58)
      - October-December (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 59)
      - This Month at the Getty (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 60)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Spring (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 61)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Summer (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 62)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin, Fall (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 63)
    - 2003:
      - January-April (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 64)
      - May-August (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 65)
      - September-December (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 66)
      - This Month at the Getty [July and December missing] (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 67)
      - Media advisories (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 68)
    - 2004:
      - January-April (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 69)
      - May-June (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 70)
      - July-December (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 71)
      - This Month at the Getty (Box 2007.IA.06-2, Folder 72)
    - 2005:
      - 2005 (Box 2007.IA.10, Folder 1)
      - Conservation Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Foundation (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Museum (Box 2014.IA.16-09)
      - Research Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Trust (Box 2014.IA.16-08)
    - 2006:
      - January-July 2006 (Box 2007.IA.10, Folder 2)
      - August-December 2006 (Box 2007.IA.10, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Foundation (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Museum (Box 2014.IA.16-09)
      - Research Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Trust (Box 2014.IA.16-08)
    - 2007:
      - Foundation (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Museum (Box 2014.IA.16-09)
      - Trust (Box 2014.IA.16-08)
    - 2008:
      - Conservation Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Museum (Box 2014.IA.16-09)
      - Research Institute (Box 2014.IA.16-10)
      - Trust (Box 2014.IA.16-08)
    - Museum-specific press releases:
      - Antiquities, 1986-1997; [2 folders] (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 1-2)
      - Drawings, 1986-1996; [2 folders] (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 3-4)
      - Manuscripts, 1986-1997; [2 folders] (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 5-6)
      - Manuscripts, special exhibits, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 7)
      - Museum, general, 1994-1996 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 8)
      - Paintings, 1985-1996 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, 1986-1997; [2 folders] (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 10-11)
      - Sculpture, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 50)
      - Trust, general, 1988-1995 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 12)
      - Trust, 1994-1996 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 13)
      - Trust, Board of Trustees, 1984-1994 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 14)
      - Art History Information Program, 1992-1995 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 15)
      - Building Program, 1986-1989 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 16)
      - Center for the History of Art and the Humanities, 1991-1995 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 17)
      - Center for Education in the Arts, 1991-1995 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 18)
      - Conservation Institute, 1987-1995 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 19)
      - Grant Program, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 20)
      - Program for Art on Film, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.06-1, Folder 21)
  - J. Paul Getty Trust, digital press materials:
    Access to digital files in 2015.IA.03, 2014.IA.16, 2016.IA.03, 2017.IA.03, 2018.IA.03, 2019.IA.03, and 2020.IA.04 is available through the links provided in the inventory.
    - 2000-2013, 2015:
      Access to digital files in 2015.IA.03 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Press releases:
        - 2000:
          - Trust
        - 2001:
          - Museum
          - Trust
        - 2002:
          - Museum
          - Trust
        - 2003:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2004:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2005:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Leadership Institute
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2006:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2007:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Publications
          - Trust
        - 2008:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2009:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2010:
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2011:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Museum
        - 2012:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
        - 2013:
          - Museum
          - Trust
        - 2015:
          - Conservation Institute
          - Foundation
          - Museum
          - Research Institute
          - Trust
      - Calendars:, 2000-2013; 2015
        General
        These calendars are published in a press-release format and were most likely intended for distribution to, and use by, media editors to advertise Getty exhibitions and events in their publications. Calendars for distribution to the general public may be found in Series IV. Calendars.
        - 2000
        - 2001
        - 2002
        - 2003
        - 2004
        - 2005
        - 2006
        - 2007
        - 2008
        - 2009
        - 2010
    - 2012-2014:
      Access to digital files in 2014.IA.16 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - 2012:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Museum
        - Foundation
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
      - 2013:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Foundation
        - Museum
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
      - 2014:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Foundation
        - Museum
        - Publications
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
    - 2016:
      Access to digital files in 2016.IA.03 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Getty 360 [public event calendar], January 2016; March-December
      - Press releases:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Foundation
        - Museum
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
    - 2017:
      Access to digital files in 2017.IA.03 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Press releases:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Foundation
        - Museum
        - Publications
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
    - 2018:
      Access to digital files in 2018.IA.03 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Press releases:
        - Conservation Institute
        - Foundation
        - Museum
        - Publications
        - Research Institute
        - Trust
    - 2019:
      Access to digital files in 2019.IA.03 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Conservation Institute
      - Foundation
      - Museum
      - Research Institute
      - Trust
    - 2020:
      Access to digital files in 2020.IA.04 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Conservation Institute
      - Foundation
      - Museum
      - Publications
      - Research Institute
      - Trust
    - 2021:
      Access to digital files in 2021.IA.04 is available online through the link provided in the inventory.
      - Conservation Institute
      - Foundation
      - Museum
      - Publications
      - Reserach Institute
      - Trust
    - 2022:
      - Conservation Institute
      - Education and Family Programs
      - Foundation
      - Museum
      - Publications
      - Research Institute
      - Trust
      - Press releases 2022 by publication date
        Scope and Contents
        spreadsheet containing titles, web links, and date of issuance.
- Press releases, subject files, 1974-2002; 2006; Series II.; 7.08 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  These press releases document events that the J. Paul Getty Trust wished to publicize to media outlets, and date from 1974 to 2002. The press releases, intended to promote Getty activities, were distributed to journalists and other members of the media by the J. Paul Getty Museum (1954-1982), the Department of Public Affairs (1983-1999), and the Communications Department (2000-present). Also present are media advisories, event calendars and fact sheets with associated press clippings and memorandums.
  Topics include acquisitions; appointments, awards, and resignations; building projects; conferences and projects; conservation and restoration; docents and volunteers; exhibitions; fellows, scholars, and interns; grant awards; operational announcements; performances and events; panels, seminars, and symposiums; publications; and others. All Getty programs, including those no longer in operation, are represented. Duplicate press releases may also appear in Series I. Chronological press releases, and Series III. Press kits. While the number of press releases is extensive, it is not presumed to be a comprehensive collection.
  The records are arranged by program and then by subject. The programs appear in the following order: Trust, Museum, Getty Conservation Institute, Center for the History of Art in the Humanities/Getty Research Institute, Center for Education in the Arts/Getty Education Institute (including the Art on Film, Museum Management Institute, and Leadership Institute programs), Art History Information Program/Getty Information Institute, and the Getty Grant Program.
  Within each subject area, the records are listed in reverse chronological order. If a listed program has been dissolved into another, every intention has been made to retain both program headings and keep the continuous chronology intact. Please note that some records in this series duplicate those found in Series I: Chronological files.
  The majority of final versions of hard-copy press releases issued by the Getty 1974-2002 have been scanned, processed using uncorrected optical character recognition (OCR), and saved as .pdf-a files. The content of each folder has been scanned as a single .pdf; depending on the contents of the folder each .pdf may be a single press release or multiple releases. The links to these electronic versions appear beneath the folder titles in the Series II inventory for the years 1974-2002; some records predating 2002 have not been scanned, nor records from 2006. Internal word-searchabiltiy of the .pdf files varies depending on the consistency of the font and on the quality and background color of the original release. Please note that all material in the folders that was not a final Getty-issued press release was not scanned, including drafts, memos, correspondence, photos, and releases issued by other organizations.
  - J. Paul Getty Trust:
    - Appointments, awards, and resignations:
      - Ken Robinson Appointed Senior Advisor, September 25, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 73)
      - Bradley Wells Named Vice President of Finance, March 21, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 75)
      - Peter Erichsen Named Vice President and General Counsel, July 19, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 74)
      - Ronald Burkle to Board of Trustees, February 1, 2001; (includes 2 diskettes) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 76)
      - New Role Announced for Deborah Marrow, August 21, 2000 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 77)
      - Barbara Fleischman and Luis Nogales New Board of Trustees, July 18, 2000; (includes 2 diskettes) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 78)
      - David Pierpont Gardner Elected Chairman, July 18, 2000; (includes 2 diskettes) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 79)
      - New Announcements: Stephen Rountree and Gwen Walden, February 17, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 80)
      - Barry Munitz Getty CEO, July 17, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 81)
      - Copy of Ira Yellin and Ramon Cortines Elected Trustees, June 24, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 82)
      - Copy of Harold Williams Announces Retirement, June 10, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 83)
      - John Cooke Elected to Trustees, January 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 84)
      - David Fisher Elected to Board of Trustees, July 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 85)
      - Lorri Starr Named Director of Public Affairs, July 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 86)
      - Christine Steiner Named General Counsel, February 8, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 87)
      - Agnes Gund Elected to Board of Trustees, February 7, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 88)
      - Blenda Wilson Elected to Board of Trustees Robert Wood Johnson Foundadion, October 7, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 89)
      - Gustav Leinhard Becomes Trustee Emeritus/Robert Myers New Chairman Columbia University, March 18, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 90)
      - Nancy Englander Announces James Kopp Editor at Columbia, June 26, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 91)
      - Harold Williams to Norton Simon Board/Jennifer Jones Simon to Getty Trust Board, February 2, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 98)
      - Harold Williams Honored, May 25, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 101)
      - Wilmer Shields Rich Award, April 24, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 102)
      - Otto Wittmann 1987 Award for Service to Museums, June 5, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 103)
    - Capital building projects:
      - Getty Center:
        For Getty Center 1997 opening press kits, see Series III. Press kits.
        - Construction Plans Made Public, September 20, 1983 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 11)
        - Architects for Fine Arts Center Narrowed to Three, April 25, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 9)
        - Acquisition of Additional 580 Acres, January 19, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 10)
        - Stephen Roundtree Director of Building Program, August 23, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 8)
        - Richard Meier to Design Arts Center, October 26, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 7)
        - Fact Sheet and Memo to News Directors, June 2, 1986; (1 copy) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 6)
        - Construction of Getty Center, 1984-1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 4)
          [Note: includes 10/9/1991 Copy of Release on Richard Meier's Design Unveiled; 7/11/1988 Release on Automated Shuttle System Selected; 5/14/1987 Release on Masterplan for Planning Commission; 6/23/1986 Release on Emmet L Wemple & Associates Selected as Landscape Architect; 2/28/1986 Release on Design Phase Begins; 2/21/1984 Release on Short List of Architects for Fine Arts Center]
        - Media Advisory: Tram Cars Begin Test Runs, June 19, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 2)
        - Getty Opens December 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 97)
      - Getty Villa:
        - Getty Malibu Closing and Bookstore Sale, July 6, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 140)
        - Getty Malibu Set to Close, February 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 141)
        - New Mission for Getty Villa, November 20, 1995; (1 copy) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 1)
        - Planners for Villa Renovation, July 6, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 3)
        - Renovated Galleries Reopened, April 13, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 143)
        - Getty Villa Re-opening, 2006
          - A Classic Returns, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          - Resources, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          - At the Getty villa, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          - Images, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          - The Ancient World, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
          - Architecture and Gardens, January 2006 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
    - Legal:
      - Statement Regarding Return of Antiquities, February 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 96)
    - Operational announcements:
      - Doors Open One Hour Earlier on Weekdays, November 29, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 92)
      - School Group Capacity has Doubled, August 31, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 93)
      - Thursday and Friday Nights: No Parking Reservations Needed, July 11, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 94)
      - "No Reservations Required" for College Students, May 15, 2000 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 95)
      - Request for Assistance with Intern Housing, August 3, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 156)
    - Performances and events:
      - Ruth Reichl Kicks off Celebrity Chef Series, April 13, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 112)
      - Performance at the Getty, "India in the Air" featuring works by L. Subramanian and Shashank, at Getty Center HMW, July 11, 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
    - Grants announced by outside institutions:
      - National Gallery of Art Release: Franklin D. Murphy Collection, June 20, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 25)
      - USC Release: USC Fellowships, October 20, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 26)
      - Copies of CA State Northridge Release: Northridge Earthquake Recovery Gift, September 1, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 27)
      - Los Angeles Public Library Release: Five Homework Centers, June 28, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 28)
      - Santa Monica College Release: Grant, March 22, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 29)
      - Los Angeles Public Library Release: Homework Centers in Three Branches, March 11, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 30)
      - USC Release: USC Announces $55 Million for Libraries, January 21, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 31)
      - Gilcrease Museum Release: $2,000,000 to Tulsa, OK Art Museums, undated (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 32)
    - Conferences and projects:
      - getty.edu Launched, February 20, 2001; (with diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 12)
      - Mars Millennium Project, November 22, 1999; (includes press clippings) (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 13)
      - Architecture LA Release: Children's Museum to Use Advisory Panel to Select Architect, October 8, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 99)
      - New Home for Object ID, September 24, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 14)
      - Getty and UCLA Masters Program in Archaeological and Ethnographic Conservation, January 12, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 15)
      - The American Assembly Release: Philanthropy in a Changing America Meeting at Getty, April 15, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 100)
      - World Bank and Getty Trust partners to sustain cultural heritage, Harold M. Williams and James D. Wolfensohn, November 4, 1997 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - Digital Press Day at Getty Center, Time and Bits: Managing Digital Community Conference at the Getty Center, February 10, 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
        [Includes invitation, schedule, list of panelists, moderator talking points, information packet]
  - J. Paul Getty Museum:
    - Appointments, awards, and resignations:
      - William Griswold Named Associate Director for Collections, August 2, 2001; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 87)
      - Deborah Gribbon Appointed Director, June 19, 2000; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 88)
      - New Staff: Thomas Rhoads and Susan DeLand, May 10, 2000 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 89)
      - Lee Hendrix Appointed Curator of Drawings, November 24, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 90)
      - Scott Schaefer Appointed Curator of Paintings, December 10, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 91)
      - Walsh and Gribbon Appointments, July 27, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 92)
      - Diane Brigham Named Head of Education, June 22, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 93)
      - Nicholas Turner Appointed Curator, February 1, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 94)
      - David Jaffe Named Curator of Paintings, January 4, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 95)
      - Deborah Gribbon Named Chief Curator/Barbara Whitney Takes on Public Information, April 23, 1991; (includes photos) (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 96)
      - Marion True Honored by Republic of Cyprus, January 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 114)
      - Myron Laskin's Resignation, January 17, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 97)
      - Brian Considine Appointed Conservator of Decortive Arts and Sculpture, January 13, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 98)
      - Gillian Wilson Receives French Award, June 22, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 99)
      - David Ebitz Named Head of Education and Academic Affairs, September 28, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 100)
      - Charles Passela Named Head of Photographic Services, May 21, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 101)
      - Judith Keller Named Associate Curator of Photographs, August 21, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 102)
      - Lori Starr Named Head of Public Information, April 25, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 103)
      - Bret Waller Named Associate Director for Education and Public Affairs, November 7, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 104)
      - Barbara Whitney Named Assistant Director, September 10, 1984; September 26, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 105)
      - Myron Laskin Curator of Paintings/ Burton Fredericksen Sr Curator, July 11, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 106)
      - Weston Naef Named Curator of Photographs, June 8, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 107)
      - Thomas Kren Named Curator of Manuscripts, April 30, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 108)
      - Peter Fusco Named Curator of Sculpture, April 30, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 109)
      - Deborah Gribbon Named Assistant Director at Museum, February 22, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 110)
      - John Walsh Named Getty Museum Director, October 19, 1983 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 111)
      - John Walsh, Jr. Accepts Position, March 3, 1983 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 112)
      - Getty Museum Director Resigns, November 22, 1982 (Box 2007.IA.34-3, Folder 113)
    - Exhibition schedules:
      - News From The Getty, Boletin Trimestral de Noticias Fall 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
        In Spanish
      - News From The Getty, Boletin Trimestral de Noticias Summer 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - News From The Getty, Boletin Trimestral de Noticias Winter 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Quarterly News Bulletin Fall 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Getty Center exhibitions listing in Spanish text, Fall, Fall 1999 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - News From The Getty, Boletin Trimestral de Noticias Fall 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
        Bulletin in Spanish
      - News From The Getty, Quarterly News Bulletin Summer 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
        2 copies- 1 in English, 1 in Spanish
      - News From The Getty, Quarterly News Bulletin Spring 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - News From The Getty, Quarterly Press Calendar Summer 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
      - Exhibitions Spring, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 121)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions, 1996-1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 122)
      - Exhibition Schedule 1996-1997: Revised, July 20, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 123)